(Penny:)- What are you waiting for?
- They're in a group. I'm scared.
(Leonard:)Sheldon,
what do you expect us to do?
(Sheldon:)You're biologists.
Biology is the study of living things.
(Sheldon:)That's a living thing. Get cracking.
(Bernadette:)I specialize in microorganisms
and Amy studies brains.
(Amy:)Yeah, neither of us minored
in bird shooing.
(Sheldon:)Oh, come, now.
Your undergraduate work...
...must've included
a varmints and critters class.
(Bernadette:)Come back in, Sheldon.
He's not gonna hurt you.
(Bernadette:)He looks friendly.
I think he might be someone's pet.
What? No, Bernadette.
Don't be a hero.
- Aw, he's a sweetie.
- Yes. He's very sweet.
(Sheldon:)Now slowly and carefully
flush him down the toilet.
(Amy:)Sheldon, the only way to get past
this fear is to interact with it.
(Amy:)Just like you did with the mailman.